dessci.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Statement

The Internet is revolutionizing both business and education. The ability to access information on millions of subjects almost instantly is a powerful tool. With that power comes the potential for abuse of personal privacy. In recognition of that potential, we have created this privacy statement. This statement is a set of promises to you with respect to how personal information you give us via the dessci.com Web site will be handled.

To protect your privacy, Design Science follows four principles in accordance with world-wide practices for customer privacy and data protection:

## **PRINCIPLE 1 - NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you register one of our products, fill out a form that adds you to a mailing list or that allows you to download free software. We use your Personal Information solely to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Design Science. We will not provide your Personal Information to any other organizations or individuals.

## **PRINCIPLE 2 - CONSENT**

If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you can still use most of dessci.com. But you will not be able to access areas or download software that requires registration.

If, at some later time, you decide that you no longer want to receive e-mail messages from us, just send a message (the subject and body of the message are ignored) to [remove@dessci.com](mailto:remove@dessci.com) and you will be permanently removed. Be sure to send it from the same e-mail account at which you no longer wish to receive messages from us. This process will not remove you from our product registration database.

## **PRINCIPLE 3 - SECURITY**

Design Science has taken strong measures to protect the security of your Personal Information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Our online ordering system uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) in all transfers to and from your computer involving your credit card information.

## **PRINCIPLE 4 - ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe Design Science has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at [support@dessci.com](mailto:support@dessci.com?SUBJECT=Privacy%20Policy), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

## **CONCLUSION**

It is our hope that our promise to adhere to these principles will allow you to use our Web site confident that your privacy is maintained. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement or privacy on this Web site, please send us email at [support@dessci.com](mailto:support@dessci.com?SUBJECT=Privacy%20Policy). Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.
